(Leonard:)So, are we doing this?
Okay, but where
does he get the helium?
(Leonard:)Remember?
Don't ask too many questions?
(Sheldon:)Uh, but this is
violating university code.
(Leonard:)A little, but...
(stammers)
(Leonard:)if I may quote Einstein,
“The pursuit of science calls us
to ignore the rules set by man”"
(Sheldon:)Huh.
(Sheldon:)All right, do it.
(Leonard:)Tell him we're in.
(Leonard typing rapidly)
(Leonard:)Done.
(Sheldon:)I can't find that quote
on the Internet.
(Sheldon:)Did you make that up?
(Leonard:)Before I answer,
(Leonard:)may I just say your skin
has never looked better.
(Sheldon:)Aren't you just made of sugar.
(Amy:)I'm not sure
how I feel about this.
(Penny:)Oh, come on, just let him
put the app on your phone.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, Stuart got
two dates with it.
(Stuart:)One of which would've ended
in sex had she not said no.
(Stuart:)Okay, all set.
(Penny:)Okay, let me see.
(clears her throat)
(Penny:)Nope, nope,